{
    "subject": "resource/184th_Pennsylvania_Infantry",
    "predicate": "ontology/battle",
    "object": "resource/Battle_of_Sutherland's_Station",
    "human_readable": "The 184th Pennsylvania Infantry was involved in the Battle of Sutherland's Station.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9887102246284485,
            "question": "Was the 184th Pennsylvania Infantry a participant in the Battle of Sutherland's Station?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.988421618938446,
            "question": "Can you provide information about the 184th Pennsylvania Infantry's role in the Battle of Sutherland's Station?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.986535370349884,
            "question": "Are there any historical accounts or records about the 184th Pennsylvania Infantry's involvement in the Battle of Sutherland's Station?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9853846430778503,
            "question": "What is the connection between the 184th Pennsylvania Infantry and the Battle of Sutherland's Station?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9829775094985962,
            "question": "Name a battle that involved the 184th Pennsylvania Infantry."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9806473851203918,
            "question": "What battle was the 184th Pennsylvania Infantry involved in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.948590099811554,
            "question": "What other battles might the 184th Pennsylvania Infantry have been involved in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8877891898155212,
            "question": "Which regiment participated in the Battle of Sutherland's Station?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7812723517417908,
            "question": "Where did the Battle of Sutherland's Station take place?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7552505731582642,
            "question": "During which historical period did the Battle of Sutherland's Station take place?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The 184th Pennsylvania Infantry was involved in the Battle of Sutherland's Station.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3045_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where did the Battle of Sutherland's Station take place?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3045_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which regiment participated in the Battle of Sutherland's Station?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3045_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What other battles might the 184th Pennsylvania Infantry have been involved in?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3045_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3045_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3045_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3045_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3045_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3045_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3045_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3045_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3045_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3045_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3045_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that the documents mention the following information related to the 184th Pennsylvania Infantry and the Battle of Sutherland's Station:\n\n* The 184th Pennsylvania Volunteer Infantry was an infantry regiment that served in the Union Army during the American Civil War.\n* The regiment was involved in various battles, including:\n\t+ Siege of Petersburg\n\t+ Second Battle of Petersburg\n\t+ First Battle of Deep Bottom\n\t+ Second Battle of Deep Bottom\n\t+ Second Battle of Ream's Station\n\t+ Battle of Boydton Plank Road\n\t+ Battle of Hatcher\u2019s Run\n\t+ Appomattox Campaign\n\t+ Battle of White Oak Road\n\t+ Battle of Sutherland\u2019s Station\n\t+ Battle of Sailor\u2019s Creek\n\t+ Battle of High Bridge\n\t+ Battle of Appomattox Court House\n* The document also mentions that the regiment was attached to 1st Brigade, 2nd Division, II Corps, Army of the Potomac.\n* The text specifically states: \"Battle of Sutherland\u2019s Station\" and lists it as one of the battles involving the 184th Pennsylvania Volunteer Infantry.\n\nTherefore, based on the information provided in the documents, it is correct to conclude that The 184th Pennsylvania Infantry was involved in the Battle of Sutherland's Station."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe context information provided mentions \"Battle of Sutherland\u2019s Station\" as one of the engagements for the 184th Pennsylvania Infantry Regiment, which supports the statement that the regiment was involved in this battle."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "The Battle of Sutherland's Station occurred on April 2, while the 184th Pennsylvania Infantry's service details provided show no engagement on that date.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Context information details battles on April 2nd, 1865 while the provided text about the 184th Pennsylvania Infantry Regiment focuses on actions leading up to and including April 9th, 1865.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The context information provided lists the battles and engagements of the 184th Pennsylvania Infantry Regiment, but the Battle of Sutherland's Station is not mentioned as one of their engagements. In fact, the text mentions that Henry Heth had ordered the remnants of his command to organize at Sutherland's Station, implying that it was a Confederate action.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context information does not list the Battle of Sutherland's Station among the engagements involving the 184th Pennsylvania Infantry Regiment.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}